const quizDataEsp = [
    {
      question: 'yo | estudiar',
      1: 'estudia',
      2: 'estudio',
      3: 'estudias',
      correct: 2,
      display: 'yo estudio'
    },
    {
      question: 'tú | hablar',
      1: 'hablo',
      2: 'hablan',
      3: 'hablas',
      correct: 3,
      display: 'tú hablas'

    },
    {
        question: 'ella | cantar',
        1: 'cantas',
        2: 'cantamos',
        3: 'canta',
        correct: 3,
        display: 'ella canta'
    },
    {
        question: 'jugar | nosotros',
        1: 'jugamos',
        2: 'jugas',
        3: 'jugáis',
        correct: 1,
        display: 'nosotros jugamos'
    },
    {
        question: 'vosotros | viajar',
        1: 'viajo',
        2: 'viajáis',
        3: 'viaja',
        correct: 2,
        display: 'vosotros viajáis'
    },
    {
      question: 'ustedes | cerrar',
      1: 'cerramos',
      2: 'cierran',
      3: 'cierra',
      correct: 2,
      display: 'ustedes cierran'
  },
  {
    question: 'nosotras | trabajar',
    1: 'trabajamos',
    2: 'tarabajan',
    3: 'trabajo',
    correct: 1,
    display: 'nosotras trabajamos'
  },
  {
    question: 'yo | tomar',
    1:'tomas',
    2:'tomáis',
    3:'tomo',
    correct: 3,
    display: 'yo tomo'
  },
  {
    question: 'ella | cenar',
    1: 'cena',
    2: 'ceno',
    3: 'cenas',
    correct: 1,
    display: 'ella cena'
},
{
  question: 'él | escuhar',
  1: 'escucha',
  2: 'escuchamos',
  3: 'escucho',
  correct: 1,
  display: 'él escucha'
}
  ];

  
  export { quizDataEsp }

  /* 
  {
    question: '|',
    1: '',
    2: '',
    3: '',
    correct:
},
*/